Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - M
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - New world order (disc one), 1998; SR-22591; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22592. Double album.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # B922304-01 A1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - New world order (disc two), 1998; SR-22592; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 365)
          In same jacket as # SR-22591. Double album.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # B922304-02 C1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - New world order, 1998; SR-22593; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          Catalog # 74321 64859 1/A; A-side Matrix # B920401-01 A1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - New world order, 1999; SR-22594; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22595. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 74321 67816 1; A-side Matrix # B923811-01 A1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - New world order, 1999; SR-22595; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22594. 2 copies.
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Global players (my name is techno) (disc one), 2000; SR-22596; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22597. Double album.
          Catalog # 74321 78842 1; A-side Matrix # B037133-01 A1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Global players (my name is techno) (disc two), 2000; SR-22597; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22596. Double album.
          Catalog # 74321 78842 1; A-side Matrix # B037133-02 C1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Nite of the tschuldigungs, 1996; SR-22598; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22599. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 08-033589-20; A-side Matrix # 08 33589 20 1A1 HYT 70254
          Hysteria
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Nite of the tschuldigungs, 1996; SR-22599; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22598. 2 copies.
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Free me, 1997; SR-22600; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          Catalog # 74321 53571 1; A-side Matrix # MR X & MR Y - A
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Viva la revolucion, 1999; SR-22601; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          Catalog # 74321 68589 1; A-side Matrix # B924004-01 A1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Global players (my name is techno) (the raver's nature and beroshima remixes), 2000; SR-22602; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          Catalog # 74321 81249 1; A-side Matrix # B040959-01 A1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - New world order, 1999; SR-22603; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          Catalog # 74321 64859 1 /A; A-side Matrix # B920401-01 A1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - What's up at the brotherfront, 1999; SR-22604; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          Catalog # 74321 70679 1; A-side Matrix # B926797-01 A1 MK
        - Mr. X & Mr. Y - Butterloops, 2001; SR-22605; Mr. X & Mr. Y (Box 366)
          Catalog # 74321 86692 1; A-side Matrix # B148776-01 A1
        - Mrs. Wood - 1-2-3-4, 1998; SR-22606; Mrs. Wood (Box 366)
          Catalog # 12 REACT 121; A-side Matrix # 12 REACT 121 A1
          React
        - MS 1 - As time goes by, 1995; SR-22607; MS 1 (Box 366)
          Catalog # MRCVIP 1047; A-side Matrix # MRCVIP-1047-A
          Viper Records
        - Ms. Jade - Girl interrupted (disc one), 2002; SR-22608; Ms. Jade (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22609. Double album.
          Catalog # 069493513-1; A-side Matrix # 069493513-1-A
          Interscope Records
        - Ms. Jade - Girl interrupted (disc two), 2002; SR-22609; Ms. Jade (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22608. Double album.
          Catalog # 069493513-1; A-side Matrix # 069493513-1-C
        - Ms. Jade - Feel the girl, 2002; SR-22610; Ms. Jade; Tweet (Box 366)
          Catalog # INTR-10683-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10683-1 RE1-A
        - Ms. Melodie - Hype according to Ms. Melodie, 1988; SR-22611; Ms. Melodie (Box 366)
          Catalog # 1156-1-JDAB; A-side Matrix # 1156-1-JD-A
        - Ms. Thing - I want it all, 2004; SR-22612; Ms. Thing (Box 366)
          Catalog # SEQ 8025-6; A-side Matrix # SEQ 8025-6-A
          Sequence Records
        - MSG - I can tell, 1987; SR-22613; MSG; Glenn "Sweety G" Toby (Box 366)
          Catalog # DI 109; A-side Matrix # DI-109-A
          Diamond Records
        - M.T. - Set it off; Comin atchya live, 1995; SR-22614; M.T. (Box 366)
          Catalog # PRO-7443-0; A-side Matrix # PRO-7443-0-A
        - M.T. - The ghetto; Hornier, 1996; SR-22615; M.T. (Box 366)
          Catalog # PRO-7448-0; A-side Matrix # PRO-7448-0-DJ-A
        - Most Talented - The magi; Tell 'em your name, 2000; SR-22616; Most Talented (Box 366)
          Catalog # ONES001; A-side Matrix # ONES-001-A-RE-1
          One Source Entertainment Inc.
        - Mtume - Breathless, 1986; SR-22617; Mtume (Box 366)
          Catalog # 49-05385; A-side Matrix # XSS-175119-1B
        - Mtume - Green light, 1983; SR-22618; Mtume (Box 366)
          Catalog # 49-04952; A-side Matrix # XSS-171529-AB
        - Mtume - Would you like to (fool around), 1983; SR-22619; Mtume (Box 366)
          Catalog # 49-04088; A-side Matrix # XXS-171347-1B
        - Mtume - Juicy fruit, 1983; SR-22620; Mtume (Box 366)
          Catalog # AS 1647; A-side Matrix # XXS-170879-1A
        - Mucho Macho - One dollar; Code break, 1999; SR-22621; Mucho Macho (Box 366)
          Catalog # WIJ 118 T; A-side Matrix # WIJ 118TA
          Wiiija Records
        - Mudfaces - 2U; Kings & queens, 1996; SR-22622; Mudfaces (Box 366)
          Catalog # 120101; A-side Matrix # 120101-A
          MFC Productions
        - Muhammad, Elijah - What the muslims want; What the muslims believe, 1965; SR-22623; Muhammad, Elijah (Box 366)
          Catalog # 15193; A-side Matrix # 15193-A
        - Muhammad, Idris - Fox huntin', 1979; SR-22624; Muhammad, Idris (Box 366)
          Catalog # F-9581; A-side Matrix # F9581-A-RE1-1F
          Fantasy Records
        - Muhammad, Idris - House of the rising sun, 1976; SR-22625; Muhammad, Idris (Box 366)
          Catalog # KU-27; A-side Matrix # RVG-98787-A-1
          Kudu
        - Muhammad, Idris - Boogie to the top, 1978; SR-22626; Muhammad, Idris (Box 366)
          Catalog # KU-38; A-side Matrix # KU38A
        - Muhammad, Idris - Peace and rhythm, 1971; SR-22627; Muhammad, Idris (Box 366)
          Catalog # PRST-10036; A-side Matrix # PRST-10036-A-2-A1
          Prestige
        - Muhammad, Idris - Dancing in the land of lovely ladies, 1979; SR-22628; Muhammad, Idris (Box 366)
          Catalog # D-148; A-side Matrix # D-148B-1A
        - Mullen, Morrissey - Life on the wire, 1982; SR-22629; Mullen, Morrissey (Box 366)
          Catalog # BEGA 33; A-side Matrix # BEAG-33-A
          Beggars Banquet
        - Mullen, Nicole C - Freedom, 2000; SR-22630; Mullen, Nicole C (Box 366)
          Catalog # EAS 12940; A-side Matrix # XSS-12940-A
          Word Entertainment
        - Mundy, Mary - Love me, love me, 1980; SR-22631; Mundy, Mary (Box 366)
          Catalog # D-31308-1; A-side Matrix # DS-31308-A
          Image Records
        - Mundy, Reg - Finger pop, 1982; SR-22632; Mundy, Reg; Reg Mundy Band (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22633. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 363; A-side Matrix # STDM-43430-1
        - Mundy, Reg - Finger pop, 1982; SR-22633; Mundy, Reg; Reg Mundy Band (Box 366)
          In same jacket as # SR-22632. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 363; A-side Matrix # STDM-43431-1
        - Munich Machine - Munich Machine, 1977; SR-22634; Munich Machine (Box 366)
          Catalog # NBLP-7058; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7058A
        - Mundy, Nick - You look like you wanna be loved, 1987; SR-22635; Mundy, Nick (Box 366)
          Catalog # 0-20764; A-side Matrix # B-28617-SH1
        - Munk Wit Da Funk - Exercize; Shadows, 1995; SR-22636; Munk Wit Da Funk (Box 366)
          Catalog # JARED95; A-side Matrix # JARED-95-A
          Illadelph Records
        - Murchison, Larry - The real thing, 1980; SR-22637; Murchison, Larry (Box 366)
          Catalog # SL 0089; A-side Matrix # SL-0089
          Sunlight Records
        - Murdock, Lydia - Superstar, 1983; SR-22638; Murdock, Lydia (Box 366)
          Catalog # TRS 3001; A-side Matrix # TRS-3001-AS
          Team Entertainment Records
        - Murdock, Shirley - As we lay, 1985; SR-22639; Murdock, Shirley (Box 366)
          Catalog # ED 5211; A-side Matrix # STED-5211-A-1
        - Murdock, Shirley - As we lay, 1985; SR-22640; Murdock, Shirley (Box 366)
          Catalog # ED 5170; A-side Matrix # STED-5170-A-1
        - Murdock, Shirley - A woman's point of view, 1988; SR-22641; Murdock, Shirley (Box 366)
          Catalog # 60791-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60791-A-1
        - Murdock, Lydia - Love on the line, 1984; SR-22642; Murdock, Lydia (Box 366)
          Catalog # TRS3006; A-side Matrix # TRS-3006-ASB
        - Murdock, Shirley - Oh what a feeling, 1988; SR-22643; Murdock, Shirley (Box 366)
          Catalog # ED 5329; A-side Matrix # STED-5329-A-1
        - Murdock, Shirley - Truth or dare, 1985; SR-22644; Murdock, Shirley (Box 366)
          Catalog # ED 5142; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5142-A-3
        - Murdock, Shirley - Go on without you, 1985; SR-22645; Murdock, Shirley (Box 366)
          Catalog # ED 5216; A-side Matrix # STED-66814A-1
        - Murphy, Charlie - Check it out, 2004; SR-22646; Murphy, Charlie (Box 366)
          Catalog # BSR-004; A-side Matrix # BSR004A
          Bitchslap Records
        - Murphy, Eddie - Till the money's gone, 1989; SR-22647; Murphy, Eddie (Box 366)
          Catalog # CAS 1864; A-side Matrix # XSS 01864A-1A
        - Murphy, Eddie - Boogie in your butt, 1982; SR-22648; Murphy, Eddie (Box 366)
          Catalog # 44-03012; A-side Matrix # XSS-170209-1B
        - Murphy, Eddie - Put your mouth on me, 1989; SR-22649; Murphy, Eddie (Box 366)
          Catalog # 44 68788; A-side Matrix # XSS-68788-B-1A
        - Murphy, Eddie - Eddie Murphy, 1982; SR-22650; Murphy, Eddie (Box 367)
          Catalog # FC 38180; A-side Matrix # AL-38180
        - Murphy, Eddie - So happy, 1989; SR-24001; Murphy, Eddie (Box 367)
          Catalog # C 40970; A-side Matrix # AL-40970-1B
        - Murphy, Eddie - Party all the time, 1985; SR-24002; Murphy, Eddie (Box 367)
          Catalog # 44-05280; A-side Matrix # XSS-173529-1B
        - Murphy, Walter - Mostly Mozart, 1979; SR-24003; Murphy, Walter (Box 367)
          Catalog # JD-11908; A-side Matrix # YD 11908A
          New York International Records
        - Murphy, Walter - A fifth of Beethoven, 1976; SR-24004; Murphy, Walter; Walter Murphy Band (Box 367)
          Catalog # PS 2015; A-side Matrix # PS2015-A
          Private Stock Records
        - Murphy, Walter - Discosymphony, 1979; SR-24005; Murphy, Walter (Box 367)
          Catalog # BXL1-3506; A-side Matrix # BXL1-3506-A
        - Mynk - Get up an' dance (dance with me), 1981; SR-24006; Mynk (Box 367)
          Catalog # POS 1205; A-side Matrix # POSSE-1205A-1666
        - Murray, Keith - Incredible, 1998; SR-24007; Murray, Keith (Box 367)
          Catalog # JDAB-42556-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-42556-1-A
        - Murray, Keith - Yeah yeah u know it, 2003; SR-24008; Murray, Keith (Box 367)
          Catalog # DEFR 15780-1; A-side Matrix # 440 077 99-1-A
        - Murray the K - Live as it happened (disc one), 1976; SR-24009; Murray the K (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24010. Double album.
          Catalog # MTK-0001-1; A-side Matrix # F4RS-0076
          IBC Records
        - Murray the K - Live as it happened (disc two), 1976; SR-24010; Murray the K (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24009. Double album.
          Catalog # MTK-0001-2; A-side Matrix # F4RS-0079
        - Musaliny-N-Maze - Blend famz, 2000; SR-24011; Musaliny-N-Maze (Box 367)
          Catalog # EAS 15171; A-side Matrix # XS-51517-1A
        - Muscle Shoals Horns - Dance to the music, 1977; SR-24012; Muscle Shoals Horns (Box 367)
          Catalog # PRO 7674; A-side Matrix # PRO-7674-AS
          Ariola America
        - Music Instructor - Super sonic, 1998; SR-24013; Music Instructor; Flying Steps (Box 367)
          Catalog # 0-44604; A-side Matrix # 0-44604-A
          Kinetic Records
        - Musical Youth - Never gonna give you up, 1983; SR-24014; Musical Youth (Box 367)
          Catalog # MCA-13965; A-side Matrix # MCA-3447-W3
        - Musical Youth - She's trouble; Incommunicado, 1983; SR-24015; Musical Youth (Box 367)
          Catalog # L33-1147; A-side Matrix # MCA-3724-FDS-3
        - Musical Youth - Pass the dutchie | Burn rubber on me (why you wanna hurt me), 1982; SR-24016; Musical Youth; Gap Band (Box 367)
          Catalog # SPEC-1320; A-side Matrix # SPEC-1320-A
          Unidisc
          Montreal, Canada
        - Musik G - No games; Rock on, 1998; SR-24017; Musik G; Underground Army (Box 367)
          Catalog # UGA 0198; A-side Matrix # UGA-0198-A
          Underground Army
        - Musique - Keep on jumpin'; In the bush, 1979; SR-24018; Musique (Box 367)
          Catalog # PRL D 163; A-side Matrix # PRL-D1-63AS
        - Mustafa - Circles, 1999; SR-24019; Mustafa (Box 367)
          Catalog # MUSRICH1; A-side Matrix # MUSRICH-A1
          Go! Beat
        - Mutant Rockers - Classical scratch, 1985; SR-24020; Mutant Rockers (Box 367)
          Catalog # BEG 127T; A-side Matrix # BEG-127T-A1
        - Mutiny - Semi-first class seat, 1980; SR-24021; Mutiny; Brailey, Jerome (Box 367)
          Catalog # AS 835; A-side Matrix # XSS167730-1B
        - Mýa - Best of me remix, 2000; SR-24022; Mýa; Jay-Z (Box 367)
          Catalog # INTR-10095-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10095-1-A
        - Mýa - Best of me, 2000; SR-24023; Mýa; Jadakiss (Box 367)
          Catalog # INTR-10056-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10056-1A/B
        - Mýa - Case of the ex (whatcha gonna do), 2000; SR-24024; Mýa (Box 367)
          Catalog # INTR-10120-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10120-1-A
        - Mýa - Movin' on, 1998; SR-24025; Mýa (Box 367)
          Catalog # INT12 95032; A-side Matrix # INT12-95032-A
        - Myers, Alicia - Do your kind of dance, 1981; SR-24026; Myers, Alicia (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24027. 2 copies.
          Catalog # L33-1743; A-side Matrix # MCA-2794-W1
        - Myers, Alicia - Do your kind of dance, 1981; SR-24027; Myers, Alicia (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24026. 2 copies.
        - Myers, Alicia - Just can't stay away; Appreciation, 1976; SR-24028; Myers, Alicia (Box 367)
          Catalog # L33-1234; A-side Matrix # MCA-4207-FDS-1
        - Mykrophone - Rapswing EP, 1989; SR-24029; Mykrophone (Box 367)
          Catalog # UNQ 107TR; A-side Matrix # UNQ-107-AA-TR
          Unyque Artists
        - Myron - Destiny, 1997; SR-24030; Myron (Box 367)
          Catalog # PR12 7834-1; A-side Matrix # PR12 7834-1 A
          Island Black Music
        - Myron - Destiny, 1997; SR-24031; Myron (Box 367)
          Catalog # 314-572 335-1; A-side Matrix # 314-572 335-1 A-HS
        - Myron - You're my everything, 1998; SR-24032; Myron (Box 367)
          Catalog # 314-572 501-1; A-side Matrix # 314-572-501-1A
        - Mystere - On the beat, 1990; SR-24033; Mystere (Box 367)
          Catalog # BZZXL 106010; A-side Matrix # BZZ XL 106010-A
          Buzz
        - Mystery Assignment - Cloud nine, 1985; SR-24034; Mystery Assignment (Box 367)
          Catalog # MET 350; A-side Matrix # MET-350-A
          Metropolis Records
        - Mystery Men - Stomp ya feet, 1995; SR-24035; Mystery Men (Box 367)
          Catalog # OD-01; A-side Matrix # OD-01-A
          Odyssey Recordings
        - Mystic Bill - Mystic files 1989-95, 1995; SR-24036; Mystic Bill (Box 367)
          Catalog # TX 5037; A-side Matrix # TX 5037 A
        - Mystic Merlin - Mr Magician, 1982; SR-24037; Mystic Merlin (Box 367)
          Catalog # SPRO-9764; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9764
        - Mystic Merlin - Mystic Merlin, 1980; SR-24038; Mystic Merlin (Box 367)
          Catalog # ST 1-12047; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12047-Z2
        - Mystidious Misfitss - Upside down (digga mix), 1995; SR-24039; Mystidious Misfitss (Box 367)
          Catalog # BAS 7325; A-side Matrix # XSS7325A-1A
          550 Music
        - Mystidious Misfitss - Upside down (world is born), 1995; SR-24040; Mystidious Misfitss (Box 367)
          Catalog # 46 78069; A-side Matrix # XSS78069A-1A
        - Mystidious Misfitss - I be, 1995; SR-24041; Mystidious Misfitss (Box 367)
          Catalog # 46 77875; A-side Matrix # XSS-77875-A
        - Mystik - Le chant de l'exilé (disc one), 1999; SR-24042; Mystik (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24043. Double album.
          Catalog # EPC4965781; A-side Matrix # EPC49657810001A1
        - Mystik - Le chant de l'exilé (disc two), 1999; SR-24043; Mystik (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24042. Double album.
          Catalog # EPC4965781; A-side Matrix # EPC4965781 C1
        - Mystikal - Y'all ain't ready yet, 1995; SR-24044; Mystikal (Box 367)
          Catalog # JDCD-42330-1; A-side Matrix # JDCD-42330-1-A1
        - Mystikal - Ghetto fabulous (disc one), 1998; SR-24045; Mystikal (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24046. Double album. Annotated.
          Catalog # JDAB-41655-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-41655-1-A
        - Mystikal - Ghetto fabulous (disc two), 1998; SR-24046; Mystikal (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24045. Double album.
          Catalog # JDAB-41655-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-41655-1-C
        - Mystikal - Tarantula (disc one), 2001; SR-24047; Mystikal (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24048; SR-24049; SR-24050. Double album; 2 copies.
          Catalog # 01242-41770-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-41770-1A
        - Mystikal - Tarantula (disc two), 2001; SR-24048; Mystikal (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24047; SR-24049; SR-24050. Double album; 2 copies.
          Catalog # 01242-41770-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-41770-1C
        - Mystikal - Tarantula (disc one), 2001; SR-24049; Mystikal (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24047; SR-24048; SR-24050. Double album; 2 copies.
        - Mystikal - Tarantula (disc two), 2001; SR-24050; Mystikal (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24047; SR-24048; SR-24049. Double album; 2 copies.
        - Mystikal - Round out the tank; Life ain't cool, 1998; SR-24051; Mystikal (Box 367)
          Catalog # JDAB-42577-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42577-1-A
        - Mystikal - Let's get ready (disc one), 2000; SR-24052; Mystikal (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24053. Double album.
          Catalog # 01241-41696-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-41696-1A
        - Mystikal - Let's get ready (disc two), 2000; SR-24053; Mystikal (Box 367)
          In same jacket as # SR-24052. Double album.
          Catalog # 01241-41696-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-41696-1C
        - MMW - Midnight birds, 2005; SR-24054; MMW; Sa-Ra (Box 367)
          Catalog # 7243 5 70410 11; A-side Matrix # BTE-70410-1A
        - MacDonald, Ralph - I need someone; Discolypso, 1979; SR-30809; MacDonald, Ralph (Box 329)
          Catalog # TKD-407; A-side Matrix # TKD-407-A-PW
        - Machine - There but for the grace of God go I, 1979; SR-30810; Machine (Box 329)
          Catalog # JD-11457; A-side Matrix # PD-11457-A
        - Mack 10 - Hoo-bangin' | Miami life, 1996; SR-30811; Mack 10; Ice Cube; Ras Kass (Box 329)
          In same jacket as # SR-30812. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SPRO 30053; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30053-AS-33016
        - Mack 10 - Hoo-bangin' | Miami life, 1996; SR-30812; Mack 10; Ice Cube; Ras Kass (Box 329)
          In same jacket as # SR-30811. Multiple copies.
        - Mantus - (Dance it) Freestyle rhythm, 1979; SR-30813; Mantus (Box 329)
          Catalog # SM-501; A-side Matrix # SMI-501-A-1
          SMI
        - Markham, Pigmeat - Here comes the judge, 1968; SR-23403; Markham, Pigmeat (Box 329)
          Catalog # LPS-1523; A-side Matrix # W4RS-3933-2A 16909-R LPS-1523 S-1
          Chess
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Rastaman vibration, 1976; SR-30814; Bob Marley & the Wailers (Box 329)
          Catalog # ILPS 9383; A-side Matrix # ILPS 9383 A PIT
        - Maxayn - Bail out for fun!, 1974; SR-30815; Maxayn (Box 329)
          Catalog # CP 0125; A-side Matrix # CP 0125 40727-1B
          Capricorn Records
          Macon, Georgia
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Give, get, take and have, 1976; SR-30816; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 329)
          Catalog # CU 5007; A-side Matrix # CU-1-5007 PE-2
          Curtom
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Give, get, take and have, 1976; SR-30817; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 329)
          Catalog # CU 5007; A-side Matrix # CU-1-5007 RE2 LW1
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Something to believe in, 1980; SR-30818; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 329)
          Catalog # RS-1-3077; A-side Matrix # T1 RS13077-CT1-AS
          RSO
        - Mc Lane Explosion - Pulstar, 1977; SR-30819; Mc Lane Explosion (Box 329)
          Catalog # TA 4702; A-side Matrix # T1 TA 4702 A-2
          Tom N'Jerry Records
        - McLaren, Malcolm - House of the blue Danube, 1989; SR-30820; McLaren, Malcolm; Malcolm McLaren and the Bootzilla Orchestra (Box 329)
          Catalog # WALTZ E4; A-side Matrix # WALTZ-4-A
          London, England
        - Merchant - Um ba yao; Let no man judge, 1978; SR-30821; Merchant (Box 329)
          Catalog # KD 562; A-side Matrix # KD-562-A
        - Mighty Duke - Do what you doing, 1979; SR-30822; Mighty Duke (Box 329)
          Catalog # DDCR 239; A-side Matrix # DDCR-239-AA
        - Buddy Miles Band - Chapter VII, 1973; SR-30823; Buddy Miles Band; Miles, Buddy (Box 329)
          Catalog # KC 32048; A-side Matrix # PAL 32048-1D
        - Glenn Miller Orchestra - In the digital mood, 1983; SR-30824; Glenn Miller Orchestra (Box 376)
          Catalog # GRP-A-1002; A-side Matrix # GRP-A-1002-A
          GRP
        - Minx - Nude in the window, 1985; SR-30825; Minx (Box 376)
          Catalog # SW 101 DJ; A-side Matrix # SW-101-A
          7 West Records
          Wayne, Pennsylvania
        - Mirage - Princes of love, 1978; SR-30826; Mirage (Box 376)
          Catalog # APL1-2777; A-side Matrix # APL1-2777A-1
        - Miranda, Carmen - South American way, 1975; SR-30827; Miranda, Carmen (Box 376)
          Catalog # CDLM 8029; A-side Matrix # CDLM 8029 A-1
          Middlesex, England
        - M.L.S. - Extra careful, 1982; SR-30828; M.L.S. (Box 376)
          Catalog # VAL 032; A-side Matrix # VAL-032-A-RE
          Charlotte Amalie
        - Morath, Max - Max Morath and his Ragtime Stompers, 1981; SR-30829; Morath, Max; Ragtime Stompers; Max Morath and his Ragtime Stompers (Box 376)
          Catalog # VSD 79440; A-side Matrix # V SD79440A-1A
          Vanguard
        - MPG - MPG, 1981; SR-30830; MPG (Box 376)
          Catalog # SP-4855; A-side Matrix # SP-04855-A-CP2
        - MF911 - Idol, the bloodsport, 1993; SR-30950; MF911 (Box 147)
          Catalog # 162 351 019-1 DJ; A-side Matrix # 162-351-019-1 A
          Next Plateau Records Inc.
        - Money Boss Players - Ghetto chronicle daily, 1994; SR-30951; Money Boss Players (Box 147)
          Catalog # S8-001; A-side Matrix # S 8001-A
          Section 8 Records
        - Moreira, Tricky - Together, 2004; SR-30952; Moreira, Tricky (Box 147)
          Catalog # BE 001; A-side Matrix # BE001-A
          Blue Elephant Recordings